{
    "multiple_choice": [
        {
            "id": 0,
            "question" : "Who won the US Open 2009?",
            "choices" : [
                "Roger Federer", "Novak Djokovic", "Andy Roddick", "Juan Martin Del Potro"
            ],
            "answer": "Juan Martin Del Potro"
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question" : "Which of the following players has not had a Grand Slam stadium named after them?",
            "choices" : [
                "Arthur Ashe", "Stefan Edberg", "Rod Laver", "Phillipe Chatrier"
            ],
            "answer": "Stefan Edberg"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question" : "What French word is used to denote a 40-40 tie during a game?",
            "choices" : [
                "Pe vux", "Deuce", "Egalite", "Tu jour"
            ],
            "answer": "Egalite"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question" : "Which of these players has never been world number one?",
            "choices" : [
                "Michael Chang", "Juan Carlos Ferrero", "Patrick Rafter", "Andy Roddick"
            ],
            "answer": "Michael Chang"
        }
    ],
    "short_answer": [
        {
            "id": 0,
            "question" : "How many Grand Slams has Federer won?",
            "answer" : "20"
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question" : "In which year did the 'Open Era' of tennis begin?",
            "answer" : "1964"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question" : "How many male Grand Slam winners are currently active?",
            "answer" : "7"
        }
    ],
    "true_or_false": [
        {
            "id": 0,
            "question" : "Andy Roddick has won the Australian Open once.",
            "answer" : false
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question" : "Roger Federers first Grand Slam win was Australian Open 2004.",
            "answer" : false
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question" : "There have been 26 different world number ones since the start of the Open Era.",
            "answer" : true
        }
    ]
}